Junior Front End Developer Resume

Vladimir Timonin

Tel: +38(098)25-37-035

E-mail: <u>vtimonin1979@gmail.com</u>

Skype: vlad i mir

Year of birth: 1979 City: Kharkov

<u>Objective</u>

Junior Front End developer position

Summary of Qualifications

11 years technical support and service in a telecommunication company 6 years development of telecommunication networks and security systems Basic knowledge/skills of programming on JavaScript and C#

Skills and knowledges

Programming languages: JavaScript, C#

Additional technologies: HTML5, CSS5, jQuery, Node.js

Development Environments and Tools: Sublime Text, Visual Studio

Source Control: GIT Databases: MongoDB

Foreign language

English Intermediate

Professional Experience

12/2016 – present time

Position: Project Engineer at "Padio-Link" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and security systems;
- development of project documentation.

11/2016 - 12/2016

Position: Project Engineer at "Ukrnaftokhimproect" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and security systems.

03/2015 - 06/2016

Position: Project Engineer at "IBC Solutions" Company, Moscow Responsibilities:

- development of building control systems;
- development of project documentation;
- corporate site support.

11/2012 - 01/2015

Position: Project Engineer at "Soyuzenergoproekt" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and systems;
- development of project documentation.

07/2001 - 11/2012

Position: Engineer at "Ukrtelecom" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- technical maintenance and service of telecommunication equipment;
- support and communications with customers.

Education

09/1996 - 06/2001

Kharkov National University of Radio Electronics. The specialist degree in Telecommunication Systems

Additional Education

01/2017 - 03/2017 A-Level "Front-End" Kharkov, 2017

Hobby

Sports, books, travels, photography